{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4799","name":"Drive Table Tennis Social Club","address":"645 Griswold St ","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Drive Detroit","licenseNumber":"078057","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Permanently Closed","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365","coords":"-83.04756,42.33028","geojson":{"id":"4799","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.047559567,42.330278432]},"properties":{"name":"Drive Table Tennis Social Club","owner":"Drive Detroit","address":"645 Griswold St ","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"078057","establishmentid":"4799","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Permanently Closed","review_frequency_days":"365","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3859","name":"Fastbreak Donut (Detroit Donut)","address":"645 Griswold St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5110","name":"Which Wich? Superior Sandwiches","address":"645 Griswold St Ste. 1300","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4449","name":"Carnival Fresh Mex","address":"645 Griswold St  Ste. 56 ","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2704","name":"Jimmy John's Sandwiches #573","address":"615 Griswold St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3791","name":"Mr. Pita","address":"615 Griswold","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5194","name":"Caucus Club","address":"150 W Congress St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622853","name":"Kwench Juice Cafe'","address":"719 Griswold","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4866","name":"Dime Store","address":"719 Griswold St Ste 180","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51623307","name":"Kwench Juice ","address":"719 Griswold Ste 10","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5039","name":"Mikes Kabob Grille","address":"719 Griswold Ste 140","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44219","inspectionDate":"2018-11-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-11-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"flies","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"Without use of trapping devices","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize trapping devices to help eliminate pests."},{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MENU(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Damaged","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Replace."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Baking and cooking equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"MICROWAVE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-01-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40283","inspectionDate":"2017-10-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Equipment/utensils","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36610","inspectionDate":"2016-09-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-09-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink bar","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-10-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4799"}}